Guide to the Stanford University, Freshman and Sophomore Programs, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Freshman and Sophomore Programs, records
1992-2012
SC0918
Stanford University. Freshman and Sophomore Programs.
8.5 Linear feet
Accession 2008-234 includes memos, 1996-98, syllabi, 2005-06, inaugural year report on the Stanford Sophomore College, 1999, departmental reports and course proposals, 1997, and student papers submitted in award competitions in the Stanford Introductory Seminars, 2005-06. Accession 2010-103 includes course files containing proposals, syllabi, and correspondence, 1992-2003; administrative files containing course evaluations, surveys, correspondence, reports, and memos, 1992-2008; and catalogs for the Stanford Introductory Seminars and Sophomore College.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
Access: student papers may not be photocopied.
Description of the Collection
Accession 2008-234 includes memos, 1996-98, syllabi, 2005-06, inaugural year report on the Stanford Sophomore College, 1999, departmental reports and course proposals, 1997, and student papers submitted in award competitions in the Stanford Introductory Seminars, 2005-06. Accession 2010-103 includes course files containing proposals, syllabi, and correspondence, 1992-2003; administrative files containing course evaluations, surveys, correspondence, reports, and memos, 1992-2008; and catalogs for the Stanford Introductory Seminars and Sophomore College.
Access Terms
Stanford Introductory Seminars.; Stanford Sophomore College.; Stanford University -- General subdivision--Curricula.;; Stanford University. Freshman and Sophomore Programs.
Collection Contents
- Records, Accession ARCH-2008-234
  - SIS [Stanford Introductory Seminars] student work award (papers considered) 2005-06 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - SIS student work award (papers considered) 2006 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - SIS student work award (papers considered) 2006 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - SOCO [Sophomore College] inaugural year report 1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Sophomore college syllabus, David Abernethy, Sept. 2006 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - SIS syllabi 2005 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Social Sciences (Anthropology, Communications, Economics) self-evaluation and/or SIS course proposals 1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Social Sciences (Political Science, Psychology, Sociology) self-evaluation and/or SIS course proposals 1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - School of Engineering (Mech. Eng.) self-evaluation and/or SIS course proposals 1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - School of Earth Sciences (Geo. and Env., Geophysics, Petroleum Eng.) self-evaluation and/or SIS course proposals 1997 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Natural Sciences (Appl. Physics, Biology, Chemistry) self-evaluation and/or SIS course proposals 1997 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Natural Sciences (Math, Physics, Statistics) self-evaluation and/or SIS course proposals 1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Humanities (Art, Asian Languages, Classics, Comp. Lit.) self-evaluation and/or SIS course proposals 1997 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Humanities (Drama, English, French & Italian, German Studies) self-evaluation and/or SIS course proposals 1997 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Humanities (History, Linguistics, Music) self-evaluation and/or SIS course proposals 1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Humanities (Philosophy, Religious Studies, Slavic, Spanish & Portuguese) self-evaluation and/or SIS course proposals 1997 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Computer Science self-evaluation and/or SIS course proposals 1996 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Memos, 1996-98 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Introductory Seminar Awards 2006-07 (1 of 3) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Introductory Seminar Awards 2006-07 (2 of 3) (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Introductory Seminar Awards 2006-07 (3 of 3) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Student Work 2007-08 ["Floating Bodies in Neutral Equilibrium" by Prof. Robert Finn and Mattie Sloss] (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Sophomore college photographs, 2013; Accession ARCH-2013-023 (Box 5)
- Records, Accession ARCH-2010-103
  - Files on courses (proposals, syllabi, correspondence) arranged alphabetically by professor: A-Ki, 1992-2003 (Box 1)
  - Files on courses (proposals, syllabi, correspondence) arranged alphabetically by professor: Ko-Ly and Shackleford-W, 1992-2003 (Box 2)
  - Files on courses (proposals, syllabi, correspondence) arranged alphabetically by professor: W-Z, 1992-2003 (Box 3)
  - Administrative files (course evaluations, surveys, correspondence, reports, memos, etc.) 1993-2008 (Box 3)
  - Administrative files (course evaluations, surveys, correspondence, reports, memos, etc.) 1992-2000 (Box 4)
  - Catalogs: Stanford Introductory Seminars and Sophomore College (Box 5)
  - Course Readers (Box 5)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2014-026; 0.25 Linear feet (1 box)
  - All We Leave (is a story) performance program (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Navigating Stanford brochures, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Sophomore College brochures, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Sophomore College photographs, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Sophomore College Staff Handbook, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Sophomore College Hopkins photographs, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Sophomore College syllabi, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - September Studies at Stanford (Box 1, Folder 8)